Guide to the Kenneth J. Arrow Papers, 1921-2017 RL.00052
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Kenneth J. Arrow papers
1921-2017
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Arrow, Kenneth J. (Kenneth Joseph), 1921-2017
RL.00052
142 Linear Feet 94 boxes
13.2 Gigabytes
Kenneth Arrow (1921-2017) was a Nobel Prize-winning economist and a professor of economics at Stanford University and Harvard University. This collection consists of his correspondence, research, writings, and other materials documenting his political and personal interests, as well as his collaborations and professional affiliations across the fields of economics, mathematics, public policy, and international relations.
Access Restrictions
The collection's correspondence is restricted for ten years following the date of its creation. Contact Research Services to request permission to view recent correspondence. This restriction expires in full by 2027.
Provenance
The papers of Kenneth J. Arrow were donated to the Duke University David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library beginning in 1978.
Biographical Note
Chronology
1921 Born in New York, NY
1940 B.S., Mathematics, City College of New York
1941 M.A., Mathematics, Columbia University
1942-1946 Weather Officer, US Army Air Corps (ret. Captain)
1947 Married Selma Schweitzer
1947-1949 Research Associate, Cowles Commission for Research in Economics
1948-1949 Assistant Professor of Economics, University of Chicago
1948- Consultant, the RAND Corporation
1949-1968 Acting Assistant Professor, Associate Professor, and Professor of Economics and Statistics, Stanford University
1951 Ph.D., Economics, Columbia University
1951 Publication: Social Choice and Individual Values
1954 Publication (with G. Debreu): Existence of Equilibrium for a Competitive Economy, Econometrica, vol. 22, pp. 265-290.
1957 Awarded John Bates Clark Medal by the American Economics Association (AEA)
1962-1963 Economist, President's Council of Economic Advisers
1968-1979 Professor of Economics, Harvard University
1972 Nobel Memorial Prize in Economic Sciences
1973 President, American Economics Association (AEA)
1980 to date Professor of Economics and Operations Research, Stanford University
1983-1986 President, International Economic Association (IEA)
2017 Feb. 21 Died in Palo Alto, California
Collection Overview
The Kenneth Arrow Papers document his career as an economist, professor, and Nobel Laureate. The collection provides an overview of his many professional activities, along with his research, writings, and collected notes regarding topics such as microeconomics, contingent valuation, social choice theory, general equilibrium analysis, the economics of information, climate change, and endogenous-growth theories. The collection also documents his collaboration and communications with prominent economists such as Robert Aumann, Gerard Debreu, Frank Hahn, John Harsanyi, Leonid Hurwicz, Harold Hotelling, Tjalling Koopmans, Alain Lewis, Lionel McKenzie, Roy Radner, Martin Shubik, Herbert Simon, Robert Solow, and many others.
Along with his own scholarship and writings, the collection documents Arrow's role as an expert witness during various legal cases involving anti-trust lawsuits, international trade, and public utilities; his professional consulting work for different groups and organizations; his political activism supporting different human rights organizations, including his involvement in agencies promoting peace in the Middle East, environmental regulation, arms reduction, and nuclear testing bans; his itineraries, lectures, and public engagements; administrative activities for various professional associations and conferences, including his leadership roles in the American Economic Association, the American Academy of Arts and Sciences, the Beijer Institute, the Econometric Society, the International Economic Association, the Office of Naval Research, the Institute of Medicine, the National Academy of Science, the National Bureau of Economic Research, and many more; and his departmental roles, committee work, and teaching contributions in the Economics Departments of Stanford University, Harvard University, and the Santa Fe Institute. The collection also contains personal artifacts and documents from Arrow's childhood and early education; awards and honorary degrees, including the Clark Medal, the National Medal of Science, and materials from the Nobel Prize ceremony; assorted books from his personal library; various foreign editions of his published works, in multiple languages; and born-digital records with his email and other working documents.
Conditions Governing Access
Electronic records in this collection have been migrated to a library server and digital use copies can only be accessed onsite in the Rubenstein Library Reading Room.
Social choice; Economics -- Sociological aspects; Economics; Contingent valuation; Economists -- United States; Social action; Equilibrium (Economics); Climatic changes; Nobel Prize winners; Lewis, Alain A.; Hurwicz, Leonid; Hotelling, Harold, 1895-; International Economic Association; Stanford University. Dept. of Economics; McKenzie, Lionel W.; Harvard University. Dept. of Economics; Hahn, Frank; Santa Fe Institute (Santa Fe, N.M.); American Economic Association
- Correspondence Series, 1954-2016 and undated
  Scope and Contents
  Contains Arrow's files on various individuals. While the series is characterized mostly by correspondence, some files are primarily correspondence with the person, while others are primarily correspondence about the person. This series also includes Arrow's correspondence with various publishers and organizations. Correspondents of note include Robert Aumann, Gerard Debreu, Milton Friedman, Frank Hahn, John Harsanyi, Leonid Hurwicz, Harold Hotelling, Tjalling Koopmans, Alain Lewis, Lionel McKenzie, Paul Samuelson, and Robert Solow.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Correspondence files are restricted for 10 years following their date of creation. Contact Research Services to request access from Arrow's family. The series will open in full by 2027.
  Electronic records in this series have been migrated to a library server and digital use copies can only be accessed onsite in the Rubenstein Library Reading Room.
  - A, Misc. Correspondence, 1973-2012; 2 folders (Box 1)
    Includes Arrow's recollections of the department of statistics at Columbia University
  - A-D, Misc. Correspondence, 1968-2013 (Box 72)
  - Abbas, Ali, 2004 (Box 1)
    Includes a discussion on von Neumann-Morgenstern Utility
  - Abramovitz, Moses, 1973-1983; 2 folders (Box 1)
    Includes remarks to his presidential address
  - Abt Books, 1982-1988 (Box 18)
  - Adam, Christopher, 1977 (Box 1)
  - Adelman, Irma, 1973-1983 (Box 1)
  - Adelstein, Richard, 1980-1988 (Box 1)
  - Admati, Anat, 1986-2004 (Box 1)
  - Ahmad, Maqsood, 1988-1989 (Box 1)
  - Akerlof, George, 1976-2001 (Box 1)
    Routine correspondence
  - Alchian, Armen, 1973-1985 (Box 1)
  - Aleskerov, Faud T., 1993-2012 (Box 1)
  - Alexander, Charles P., undated (Box 1)
  - Allais, Maurice, 1978-1992 (Box 1)
    Includes copies of Allais' papers sent to Arrow and routine correspondence
  - Allen, Beth, 1982-1989 (Box 1)
  - Allen, William R., 1985-1986 (Box 1)
  - Alt, James, 1998 (Box 1)
    Includes recollections of von Neumann, Wald, Morgenstern, Schlesinger, and the Vienna Circle
  - Amadae, Sonja M., 1995-2000 (Box 1)
  - Amemiya, Takeshi, 1985-1993 (Box 1)
  - Amsel, Georges, 1980-1981 (Box 1)
    Includes discussions on the proliferation of nuclear weapons
  - Anderson, Robert M., 1980-1982 (Box 1)
  - Andrade, Joaquim P. de, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Antoniadou, Elena, 1993-2003 (Box 1)
  - Aoki Memorial, 2015 (Box 1)
  - Aoki, Masahiko, 1987-1999 (Box 1)
  - Araújo, Aloísio P., 1977-1979 (Box 1)
  - Archibald, Christopher, 1979-1996 (Box 1)
  - Arney, Richard, 1991-1996 (Box 1)
  - Arora, Seema, 2012-2015 (Box 1)
  - Arrow, Selma, 2015 (Box 1)
  - Arrow-Hahn Book, 1985-1995; 2 folders (Box 1)
    Includes correspondence with publisher and notes on revisions for a second edition
  - Arthur, W. Brian, 1992-1998; 2 folders (Box 1)
    Includes routine correspondence and a draft foreword to Arthur's book on increasing returns
  - Atkinson, Anthony, 1994 (Box 72)
    Includes letter discussing teaching a course on income distribution.
  - Attali, Jacques, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Augier, Mie, 1999-2005 (Box 1)
  - Aumann, Robert, 1973-2008; 2 folders (Box 1)
    Includes Arrow's nomination of Aumann and Lloyd Shapley for the Nobel in economics, a brief exchange on the compatability of evolutionary theory and rational behavior, and routine correspondence
  - Aumann, Robert, 2003-2011 (Box 72)
  - Aumann-Rips, 1991 (Box 1)
  - Ausubel, Lawrence Marc, 1984 (Box 1)
  - B, Misc. Correspondence, 1965-1978 (Box 1)
  - Ba-Be, 1979-1997 (Box 1)
  - Ba-Bek, 1998-2009 (Box 1)
  - Bacharach, Michael, 1976-1998; 3 folders (Box 2)
  - Backhouse, Roger, 2015 (Box 2)
    Includes correspondence between Arrow and Backhouse about Paul Samuelson
  - Baily, Nathan, 1993 (Box 2)
  - Baker, Erin, 2000 (Box 2)
  - Baker, John Charles, undated (Box 2)
  - Balinski, Michel, 1981-1982 (Box 2)
  - Bangert, Harold W., 1981-1982 (Box 2)
  - Barclay, Michael J., 1983-1986 (Box 2)
  - Basil Blackwell Publisher (Olivieri, Rene), 1982-1983 (Box 18)
  - Basu, Kaushik, 1994-1995 (Box 2)
  - Bateman, Bradley W., 1988 (Box 2)
  - Bauer, Peter Lord, 1988-1989 (Box 2)
  - Baumol, William J., 1981-2000 (Box 2)
  - Beaver, Ron, 1995 (Box 2)
  - Becker, Guity, 2014 (Box 2)
  - Bel-Bl, 1957-2006 (Box 1)
  - Bell Journal Survey, 1976 (Box 72)
  - Bell, Daniel, 1978-1989 (Box 2)
  - Beltramo, Daniel, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Bennett, Victor, 2002-2006 (Box 2)
  - Bergmann, Barbara, 1994-2006 (Box 2)
  - Bergmann, Barbara, 1994 (Box 72)
  - Berman, José, 1980-1986 (Box 2)
  - Bernheim, Douglas, 1987-1993 (Box 2)
  - Bester, Alan, 2003 (Box 2)
  - Bewley, Truman, 1977 (Box 2)
    Includes routine correspondence
  - Bhagwati, Jagdish, 1978-1993; 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Bh-By, 1980-1996 (Box 1)
  - Biggar, Darryl R., 1992 (Box 2)
  - Bilir, Kamran, 2007-2014 (Box 2)
  - Binmore, Ken, 1986-2002 (Box 2)
  - Birardi, Franco, 1986-1995; 3 folders (Box 2)
  - Bjerkholt, Olav, 2009 (Box 2)
  - Bjerval, 1983 (Box 2)
  - Bjerve, Rannveig, 2009 (Box 2)
  - Blackwell, David, 1995-2012 (Box 2)
  - Blanco, Dr. Cicely Woods, 1984-1990 (Box 2)
  - Bm-Bz, 1972-2011 (Box 2)
  - Bockman, Johanna K., 2007 (Box 2)
  - Boldrin, Michele, 1989-1994 (Box 2)
  - Boorman, Scott, 1973-2006; 6 folders (Box 2)
  - Borzekowski, Ron, 2000-2001 (Box 3)
  - Borzekowski, Ron (limited network connections and inequality), 1999-2004; 2 folders (Box 3)
    Includes correspondence, drafts, and notes on limited network connections and income inequality research
  - Bower, Joseph, 1991 (Box 3)
  - Bowles, Samuel, 1978-2008 (Box 3)
    Includes brief correspondence on work in Marxian theory of value and other routine correspondence
  - Boxer, Nancy, 1974 (Box 3)
  - Bradford, David, 1970-1974 (Box 3)
  - Bradford, Richard, 1989-1993 (Box 3)
  - Brandenburger, Adam, 1986-1991 (Box 3)
  - Brannon, Kevin, 1994 (Box 3)
  - Bray, Margaret, 1995 (Box 3)
  - Breit, William, 1984-1986 (Box 3)
  - Brenner, Reuven, 1982-1990 (Box 3)
  - British Academy, 2006-2013 (Box 72)
  - Brock, Horace W., 1974-1993; 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Brock, William A., 1983-1998 (Box 3)
  - Brode, John, 1978-1979 (Box 3)
  - Broome, John, 1983-1994 (Box 3)
  - Brown, Donald, 1982-1991 (Box 3)
  - Browne, Elisabeth A., 1992-1996 (Box 3)
  - Bubna, Amit, 1997-1999 (Box 3)
  - Burgess, Robin, 1996 (Box 3)
  - Burk, David M., 2005 (Box 3)
  - Business in Contemporary World, 1987-1990 (Box 72)
  - Byrne, Patrick, 2010 (Box 3)
  - C, Misc. Correspondence, 1974-2009; 3 folders (Box 3)
  - Cambridge University Press, 1990-1996 (Box 18)
  - Cambridge University Press, 2012 (Box 72)
  - Campbell, Donald, 1971-1999; 3 folders (Box 3)
  - Capron, William, 2002 (Box 3)
  - Cardell, Nicholas Scott, 1979-1989 (Box 3)
  - Carlton, Dennis WM., 1971 (Box 3)
  - Carter, Anne, 2009 (Box 3)
    Includes correspondence on a Committee on the Status of Women in the Economics Profession (CSWEP) interview with Carter
  - Caspar, President Gerhard, 1993 (Box 3)
  - Cass, David, 1991-2001 (Box 3)
    Includes correspondence about edited volume on General Equilibrium compiled by Debreu
  - Castelli, Carlos, 1995 (Box 3)
  - Chang, David, 1990-1992 (Box 3)
  - Chang, Dr. Chih, 1988 (Box 3)
  - Chang, Sheldon, 1979-1989 (Box 3)
  - Chatterji, Manas, 2013 (Box 3)
  - Chenery, Hollis, 1975-1991 (Box 3)
    Includes correspondence about OPEC and balance of payments
  - Cheung, Ryner, 1988 (Box 3)
  - Chiang, Alpha, 1982 (Box 3)
    Includes correspondence on transversality conditions in infinite-horizon problems
  - Chichilnisky, Graciela, 1975-2012; 3 folders (Box 3)
    Includes correspondence on terms of trade, economic development, and general equilibrium
  - Chichilinsky, Graciela, 1992-1994 (Box 72)
  - Chikan, Attila, 1987-2007 (Box 4)
  - Chinn, Dr. Dennis, 1986 (Box 4)
  - Chipman, John S., 1975-1993 (Box 4)
  - Chomsky, Noam, 1987-1988 (Box 4)
    Includes correspondence about the Faurisson affair
  - City College New York, 1983-2006 (Box 72)
  - Clarke, Richard, 1977; 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Clay, Karen, undated (Box 4)
  - Clower, Robert W., 1979 (Box 4)
  - Coase, Ronald, 2007 (Box 4)
    Includes an invitation to a conference on China's economic transition
  - Colander, David, 1997-1998 (Box 4)
    Includes correspondence on the Commission of Graduate Education in Economics (COGEE) Report
  - Complexity, 1999 (Box 72)
  - Cooper, Leon N., 1989 (Box 4)
  - Cooter, Robert D., 1973-2012 (Box 4)
  - Costrell, Robert, 1978-1999; 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Costrell, Robert (Income determination: or, what Keynes means to me), 1978 (Box 4)
  - Coughlin, Peter, 1980-1991 (Box 4)
  - Courtillot, E. P., 1986 (Box 4)
  - Courtillot, Professor Vincent, 1993 (Box 4)
  - Crampton, Graham R., 1971 (Box 4)
  - Cutler, David, 2001-2009 (Box 4)
  - D, Misc. Correspondence, 1972-2011; 3 folders (Box 4)
  - Daily, Gretchen, 2002-2005 (Box 4)
  - Daly, Herman, 1980 (Box 4)
    Includes correspondence on Georgescu-Roegen and economics taking account of natural resources
  - D'Amico, Thomas F., 1983 (Box 4)
  - Dantzig, George B., 1985-2002 (Box 4)
  - Dasgupta, Partha, 1973-2016; 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Dasgupta, Partha, 2005 (Box 72)
  - Datta, Shouman, 1995-2003 (Box 4)
  - David, Paul, 1979-2008; 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Davidson, Paul, 1972-1974 (Box 4)
    Includes correspondence on uncertainty and risk in monetary economies
  - Davis, Donald B., undated (Box 4)
  - Day, Colin, 1987 (Box 4)
  - Day, Richard H., 1975-1996 (Box 4)
    Includes correspondence on economic dynamics and chaos
  - De Croix, Gregory A., 1991 (Box 4)
  - De Marzo, Peter M., 1985 (Box 4)
  - De Viliers, Meiring, 1996-1997 (Box 4)
  - Deaker, James, 1999 (Box 4)
  - Deaton, Angus, 2005 (Box 4)
  - Debreu, Gerard, 1953-2005; 2 folders (Box 4)
    Includes correspondence about publication of Arrow and Debreu (1954), "Existence of an Equilibrium for a Competitive Economy," as well as routine correspondence
  - Debreu, Gerard, 1998 (Box 72)
  - Deming, 1991 (Box 4)
  - Demsetz, Harold, 1986 (Box 4)
  - Despres, Emile, 1973 (Box 4)
  - Detweiler, Randy, 2013 (Box 4)
  - Diamond, Peter, 1997-2010 (Box 4)
  - Dieffenbach, Bruce, 1977-1980 (Box 4)
  - Dieffenbach, Bruce, 1970-1972 (Box 72)
  - Diewert, W. Erwin, 1979-1994 (Box 4)
  - Dionne, Georges, 1980-1989 (Box 4)
  - Dixit, Avinash, 1985 (Box 4)
  - Dohner, Robert S., 1972-1973 (Box 4)
  - Douglas, Aaron J, Biographical Sketch, undated (Box 4)
  - Douglas, Aaron J., 1977-1996; 4 folders (Box 4)
  - Dowe, David, 1984 (Box 5)
  - Drèze, Jean, 1991 (Box 5)
  - Dudkin, Professor Lev, 1981-1989 (Box 5)
  - Duffie, Darrell, 1984-1992 (Box 5)
  - Duke Library, 1985-2015 (Box 5)
  - Duran, Xavier, 2010 (Box 5)
  - Duriseti, Kristin, 1999 (Box 5)
  - Durlauf, Steven, 1992-2011; 2 folders (Box 5)
    Includes correspondence on Social Interactions and Economic Outcomes Research Network and routine correspondence
  - Dutta, Shouman, 1995-2003 (Box 5)
  - E, Misc. Correspondence, 1974-2008; 2 folders (Box 5)
  - E-H, Misc. Correspondence, 1981-2016 (Box 72)
  - Eboli, Mario, 1995-2002 (Box 5)
  - Economic Journal, 1986-2003 (Box 72)
  - Economics and Philosophy, 1994 and undated (Box 72)
  - Economides, Nicholas, 1989-2009 (Box 5)
  - Edward Elgar, 1999-2000 (Box 72)
  - EGEA, 2001 (Box 72)
    Correspondence with publisher
  - Ehrlich, Paul, 1993-2004 (Box 5)
  - Eliasson, Gunnar, 1973-2009; 2 folders (Box 5)
  - Ellsber, Daniel, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Elsevier Publishing Company, 1973-1974 (Box 18)
  - Elsevier Publishing Company, 1999-2015 (Box 72)
  - Elston, Julie Ann, 1994-1997 (Box 5)
  - Engelbrecht, Richard, 1977 (Box 5)
  - Enthoven, Alain, 1991-2001 (Box 5)
  - Entropy, 2005-2006 (Box 72)
  - Epstein, Joshua, 1999-2006 (Box 5)
  - Erickson, James, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Ersel, Hasan, 1980-1981 (Box 5)
  - Etheredge, Lloyd S., 1982-1992 (Box 5)
  - Euclid, Joe Jonah, 1988-2002 (Box 5)
  - European Journal of the History of Economic Thought, 1992-2001 (Box 72)
  - F, Misc. Correspondence, 1975-2014; 2 folders (Box 5)
  - Fang, Weiwu, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Feiger, George, 1975 (Box 5)
  - Feinberg, Yossi, 1995-2008 (Box 5)
  - Feiwel, George R., 1982-1990; 2 folders (Box 5)
  - Feldstein, Martin, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Fels, Rendigs, 1975 (Box 5)
  - Ferber, Marianne A., 1978-1990 (Box 5)
  - Fernando, Luis, 1995 (Box 5)
  - Fischbeck, Paul, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Fischer, Stanley, 1981-2001 (Box 5)
    Includes correspondence on the role of economists in society
  - Fisher, Anthony, 1978 (Box 5)
  - Fisher, Franklin, 1982-1993 (Box 5)
  - Fitoussi, Jean-Paul, 1984 (Box 72)
  - Fogel, Robert, 1990-2013 (Box 5)
  - Foley, Duncan, 2003 (Box 5)
  - Foley, Thomas F., 1994 (Box 5)
  - Fontaine, Philippe, 1999-2003 (Box 5)
  - Frank, Robert, 1995 (Box 5)
  - Freeman, Richard, 1994 (Box 5)
    Includes correspondence on discontinuous change
  - Frey, Bruno, 1984-2001 (Box 5)
  - Friedman, Milton, 1973-2002; 2 folders (Box 5)
    Includes correspondence on Arrow's review of Free to Choose and other routine correspondence
  - Fuchs, Victor R., 1980-1982 (Box 5)
  - Futia, Carl, undated (Box 5)
  - G, Misc. Correspondence, 1971-2008; 3 folders (Box 6)
  - Galbraith, James K, 2002-2006 (Box 6)
  - Galbraith, John Kenneth, 1972-2006 (Box 6)
    Includes correspondence on The Nature of Mass Poverty by Galbraith and other routine correspondence
  - Games and Economic Behavior, 1997 (Box 72)
  - Gans, Joshua, 1989-2011 (Box 6)
  - Garber, Alan, 1981-1998 (Box 6)
  - Geanakoplos, John, 1978-2003; 3 folders (Box 6)
    Includes correspondence on capital theory and rates of interest and profit, Sraffian economics, and other routine correspondence
  - Geevarghese, Anna Susan, 1991 (Box 6)
  - Gelband, Hellen, 2013 (Box 6)
  - Gevers, Louis, 1967-1971 (Box 6)
  - Ghosh, Suman, 2001 (Box 6)
  - Giarini, Orio, 1977-1979 (Box 6)
  - Gibbard, Allan, 1981-2005 (Box 6)
  - Gibbons, Robert, 1977-1980 (Box 6)
  - Gilligan, A., 2009 (Box 6)
  - Ginsburg, Bill, 1970-2006 (Box 6)
  - Gintis, Herbert, 1991 (Box 6)
  - Ginzberg, Eli, 1980-1991 (Box 6)
  - Glustoff, Earl, 1971-1978 (Box 6)
  - Goldman, Beila S., 1984-1994; 5 folders (Box 6)
  - González, Arturo R., 2002-2003 (Box 6)
  - Gordon, Nancy, 1966-1974 (Box 6)
  - Gordon, Robert, 1997 (Box 6)
  - Gordon, Tracy, 1992 (Box 6)
  - Gorman, William (Terence) M., 1980-1987 (Box 6)
  - Gould, F. J., 1973-1977 (Box 6)
  - Gould, Mark, 1973-1987 (Box 6)
  - Gould, Stephen J., 1989-1992 (Box 6)
  - Grandmont, Jean-Michel, 1974-1991 (Box 6)
  - Granger Translation, 2000 (Box 18)
    Correspondence on Granger's translation of previously published work
  - Granger, Thierry, 1998 (Box 6)
  - Green, Jerry, 1973-1983; 2 folders (Box 6)
    Includes correspondence on incomplete contingent markets and other routine correspondence
  - Greenberg, Joseph, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Grossman, Sanford, 1980-1988 (Box 6)
  - Guesnerie, Roger, 1979-2000 (Box 6)
  - Gul, Faruk, 1992-1993 (Box 6)
  - Gurfel, Benor, 1976-1977 (Box 6)
  - H, Misc. Correspondence, 1974-2014; 3 folders (Box 7)
  - Haavelmo Seminar, 2005 (Box 72)
  - Haavelmo, Trygve, 1989-1999 (Box 7)
  - Hadfield, Gillian K., 1984-2000 (Box 7)
  - Ha-He, 1978-2010 (Box 7)
  - Hahn, Frank, 1972-1013; 4 folders (Box 7)
    Includes correspondence on developments in general equilibrium theory, co-authored work, Sraffa/neo-Ricardianism, and other routine correspondence
  - Hahn, Frank, 1992 (Box 72)
  - Hamburg, D., 2010 (Box 7)
  - Hammond. Peter, 1988-2009; 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Han, Aaron K., 1983 (Box 7)
  - Harcourt, Dr. Geoffrey, 1978-2000 (Box 7)
  - Harris, Donald, 1981-1987 (Box 7)
  - Harris, Jeffrey, 1979-1985 (Box 7)
  - Harris, Milton, 1980-1987 (Box 7)
  - Harriss, C. Lowell, 1991-2010 (Box 7)
  - Harsanyi, John C., 1984-2002; 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Hart, Oliver, 1981-2002 (Box 7)
  - Harvard University Press, 1982-1984; 2 folders (Box 18)
  - Harvard University Press, 1982 (Box 72)
  - Hassin, Rafael, 1982-1983 (Box 7)
  - Hayabusa, Nagahara, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Hayashi, Toshihiko, undated (Box 7)
  - Heal, Geoffrey, 1982-1994 (Box 7)
  - Heckman, James, 1980-2000 (Box 7)
  - Heiner, Ron, 1983-1988 (Box 7)
  - Heller, Walter P., 1970-2001; 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Helpman, Elhanan, 1973-1985 (Box 7)
  - Hess, Jim, 1980-1988 (Box 7)
  - Hewlett - Jotzo-Pezzey, 2004 (Box 72)
  - Hicks, John R., 1979-2008 (Box 7)
  - Hicks, Michael, 1971-1981; 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Hillas, John, 1986-1992 (Box 7)
  - Hiromatsu, Takeshi, undated (Box 7)
  - Hirschman, Albert O., 1979-1989 (Box 7)
  - Hirshleifer, Jack, 1981 (Box 72)
  - Hirshleifer, Professor Jack, 1978-1989 (Box 7)
  - Holden-Day Publishing, 1969-1979; 4 folders (Box 18)
  - Holland, John, 1989-1992 (Box 7)
  - Hollander, Samuel, 1991 (Box 7)
  - Hollis, Martin, 1979 (Box 7)
  - Holstrom, Bengt, 1983-1988 (Box 7)
  - Honkapohja, Seppo, 1982-1992 (Box 7)
  - Hotelling Bio, 2005 (Box 7)
  - Hotelling Obituary, 1924-1988; 2 folders (Box 7)
    Includes correspondence on obituary for Harold Hotelling
  - Hotelling, Harold, 1874-1979 (Box 7)
    Includes correspondence on Hotelling's influence on Arrow
  - House of Commons, 1995 (Box 72)
  - Hu, Wei-Yin, 1989 (Box 8)
  - Huang, Peter, 1977-2009; 4 folders (Box 8)
  - Hudson, Ed, undated (Box 8)
  - Hurwicz, Leonid, 1978-2009; 2 folders (Box 8)
    Includes correspondence on stability of equilibrium and other routine correspondence
  - Hurwicz, Leo, 1996-2008 (Box 72)
  - Hussey, Deborah, 1998-1999 (Box 8)
  - Hylland, Aanund, 1980-1989 (Box 8)
  - I, Misc. Correspondence, 1972-2002; 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Industrial and Coporate Change, 1993 (Box 72)
  - International Journal of Peace Economics, 2014 (Box 72)
  - Intriligator, Michael, 1980-2016; 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Intriligator, Michael, 1997 (Box 72)
  - Irwin (Mosby-Times Mirror), 1982-1993 (Box 18)
  - Ishikawa, Tsuneo, 1971-1992; 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Ito, Takatoshi, 1980-1994 (Box 8)
  - J, Misc. Correspondence, 1977-2004; 3 folders (Box 8)
  - Jamison, Dean, 1968-2008; 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Jha, Saumitra, 2006 (Box 8)
  - Jia, Hu, 2010 (Box 8)
  - Jimbo, Ichiro, 1974-2012; 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Johns Hopkins University Press, 1979-1989 (Box 18)
  - Jonscher, Charles, 1978-1982; 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Jorgenson, Dale, 1978-1999 (Box 8)
    Includes correspondence on energy in macroeconomic models, research on poverty, and other routine correspondence
  - Journal of Economic Literature, 1991 (Box 72)
  - Journal of Health Politics, Policy and Law, 2002 (Box 72)
  - Journal of Mathematical Economics, 1996-2002 (Box 72)
  - Jubeir, Maher, 1987-1991 (Box 8)
  - K, Misc. Correspondence, 1973-2005; 3 folders (Box 8)